# ERMEK BARMASHEV

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

+1 647 631 4848
BARMASHEV48@GMAIL.COM
WWW.ERMEKCODES.COM
GITHUB.COM/BARMASHEV

# SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
- Vanilla JavaScript, JQuery, React
- Working with RESTful APIs
- Firebase database
- Responsive Design
- Web accessibility
- Version control and collaboration using Git and GitHub
- Familiar with Node JS, Express JS, Mongo DB, TypeScript

# PROFILE

I am a front end developer with experience in customer service and sales/marketing who is committed to making the web more accessible and user friendly. I love writing clean code and learning new technologies as well as collaborating with team members on the projects.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### **CASHIER**

SUMMERHILL MARKET | FEB 2020 - OCT 2020

- Promptly scanned items and collected payments,
- Using scanning devices, answering to customer inquiries in a an efficient, friendly manner
- Successfully trained new cashiers

#### MARKET STRATEGY AND PLANNING INTERN

PROCTER & GAMBLE KAZAKHSTAN | FEB 2019 - MAY 2019

- Managed Oral Care category in Kazakhstan
- Successfully worked with the marketing and distribution team to launch a new line of oral care products for the Central Asian Market
- Created and presented market overview to the Regional Director to assist in the onboarding process
- Managed distribution in key supermarket chains to increase brand visibility

# EDUCATION

#### IMMERSIVE WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP

JUNO COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY | 2020 - 2021 TORONTO, CANADA

# **BACHELOR OF INTERNATIONAL LAW**

AL-FARABI KAZAKH NATIONAL UNIVERSITY | 2012 - 2016 ALMATY, KAZAKHSTAN

# FEATURED PROJECTS

#### LIKELY MATCH

BASED ON A USER INPUT GENERATES A PLAYLIST OF SIMILAR SONGS AND STORES IT IN FIREBASE DATABASE LIVE GITHUB REPO

#### **BLACK JACK**

A GAME OF BLACK JACK THAT DEALS CARDS TO THE PLAYER AND A DEALER, COUNTS THE CARDS AND DISPLAYS THE WINNER

LIVE GITHUB REPO